Victory in brotherhood.
Come Out Fighting is a war, drama film directed by Steven Luke.
In WWII, a squad of U.S.
African-American soldiers are sent on a rescue mission behind enemy lines to
locate their lost commanding officer and a downed fighter pilot.
Frank Ross, played by Kellan Lutz.
Major Chase Anderson, played by Dolph Lundgren.
Captain Jackson, played by Aaron Courteau.
Sgt. Thomas, played by Vicellous Shannon.
Robert Hayes, played by Hiram A. Murray.
Sergeant AJ 'Red' McCarron, played by Michael Jai White.
Out Come the Wolves is a 2024 Canadian horror thriller film directed by Adam MacDonald and
scripted by Enuka Okuma from a story by MacDonald, Okuma and Joris Jarsky.
It stars Missy Peregrym, Jarsky, and Damon Runyan.
The story follows a group of friends whose camping trip turns into a nightmare
when they are stalked by a pack of wolves in a remote forest.
Out Come the Wolves was released by Altitude Film
Entertainment, on August 30, 2024.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of world war ii, us army,
american soldiers, black soldier.
The tone is emotional.